

# **ALEXANDRA CANGE**

### **JUNIOR DATA SCIENTIST**

1

+49 174 7453284

in

<u>LinkedIn</u>



alexandracange@gmail.com



Github Portfolio

2

Berlin, Germany

## PROFILE

Ex-Operations Manager, I decided to make a big career change and to start in Tech. After 5 years in Operations and exploring my leadership and organisational skills, I wanted to do something more related to datas and IT. That where my journey began. I am now a student in a Data Sciences Bootcamp at WBS School and hope to get my first entry-level position from February.

## **EDUCATION**

DATA SCIENCES WBS CODING SCHOOL, BERLIN

09.2022 - 01.2023 Project based, practice oriented, remote,

collaborative coding training

BACHELOR PUBLIC UNIVERSITY, ORLEANS

09.2013 - 07.2016 Languages, International Business and

Commerce, International Management

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **VIU EYEWEAR, MUNICH**

04.2021 -05.2022

#### SENIOR OPERATIONS MANAGER

- Effectively directed and oversaw staff of 25+ employee, designing schedules to meet the needs of the department as well as the needs of employees.
- Implemented a new inventory analysing system resulting saving 20% of spent time.

# 01.2020 - **SWQ (Shipping, Warehouse, Quality Control)**03.2021 **MANAGER**

- Maintained detailed records of stocks, incoming goods and shipments.
- Evaluate productivity, implemented new processes and tracking processes systems resulting a better organisation and KPIs.

#### 01.2019 - SHIPPING SUPERVISOR

12.2019

- Supervised up to 10 shipping employees
- Ensure all outbound orders are processed within 1.5 day

#### 10.2017 - **OPERATIONS SPECIALIST**

12.2018

Assist to company goals and operational excellence.

#### KIABI, ORLEANS

06.2016 -09.2016

#### INTERNSHIP ASSISTANT MANAGER

• Analysed with Excel and reported on the NPS to management and director.

# **TECH SKILLS**

- Python
- SOL
- Tableau
- AWS
- Machine Learning
- Web-Scrapping
- API
- Data Visualisation
- HTML
- CSS

# **PERSONNAL SKILLS**

- Fast Learning
- Problem Solving
- Adaptability
- Stress Tolerance
- Leadership

# **LANGUAGES**

- FRENCH C2/Native
- ENGLISH C1
- GERMAN B2